http://www.cleanedge.com/privacy-policy

Jump to navigation
Back to topStock IndexesOverviewCELSGWEHHOQGRDgridCONNEXT2020201920182017ResearchLatest ResearchArchived ResearchAbout UsAboutTeamPress ReleasesIn the NewsContact Us
Back to topClean Edge Privacy Policy & Disclaimers
Clean Edge is committed to protecting and respecting your privacy. We recognize that when you provide us with information about yourself, you trust us to act in a responsible manner. The following discloses our information gathering and usage practices for our website www.cleanedge.com, newsletters, alerts, and other services (Clean Edge). Please read the following closely to understand our practices. Types of Data CollectedWe may collect personally identifiable information from you that may include your name, address, e-mail address, company or organization, position or title, company size, company type, what report you downloaded and other information. We do not, however, knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of thirteen. This information is sent to and stored by MailChimp and used by Clean Edge to send bulk emails.Furthermore, we automatically collect non-personally identifiable IP addresses and web site usage information from you when you visit Clean Edge. This information is sent to Google Analytics and helps Clean Edge track site traffic and optimizes the user experience. If you wish to unsubscribe from Clean Edge emails, you may do so by using this link or by following the unsubscribe instructions included in Clean Edge electronic mailings. You may also contact us at any time to request your data be deleted from our website or MailChimp.Use of Data Collected We use contact data to send you free reports and newsletters, information about our company or our products or services, and promotional material from some of our partners, or to contact you when necessary. We do not sell, rent, or swap your name, address, or other personal information with our sponsors or other parties. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential.Use of Cookies Clean Edge uses cookies, which are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. Our site uses cookies in order to streamline the process for accessing public reports and viewing other resources.  LinksOur website and newsletters may contain links to other sites that are not owned or controlled by Clean Edge. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites and companies. Please read the privacy statements of other websites to understand their policies and handling of your information. Legal Disclaimer and SecurityClean Edge takes appropriate precautions to protect our users’ information. However, no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100 percent secure. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.We may disclose your personally identifiable information, as required by law, and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process.Financial Disclaimer  Information from Clean Edge is provided for informational and educational purposes only, and should not be construed as investment advice, either on behalf of a particular financial product or an overall investment strategy. Clean Edge, Inc., does not make any recommendation to buy or sell any financial product or any representation about the financial condition of any company or fund. Changes to Our Privacy PolicyAny changes to our privacy policy will be posted on this page and, when appropriate, you may be notified by email.ContactIf you have questions or comments regarding our privacy policy, please contact us.
